A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.9-SG 1.13 (A83-A87) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 83), 1961-1991; 1970-1982; 1.9; 90.59 Cubic Feet; 224 letter-size document boxes, 10 legal-size document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, 1 half-legal document box, and 1 15-11.5 oversized document box
  - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases (ILRAD), 112
    - Organization and Planning - Consultants (A-Z), 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 322)
      W. Alistair Greig; F. W. Jennings; W. Ian McIntyre; Bruce McKenzie; W. R. Pritchard; George M. Urquhart
  - International Livestock Centre for Africa (ILCA), 113
    - Organization and Planning, 1969-1980 (Box 45, Folder 323-327, Box 46, Folder 328)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 115
    - Administration, 1969-1979 (Box 46, Folder 329-331)
    - Board of Trustees, 1970-1978 (Box 46, Folder 332-333, Box 47, Folder 334-336)
    - Financial, 1970-1977, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 337-338)
    - Financial: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 47, Folder 339-340, Box 48, Folder 341-343)
    - Organization and Planning, 1970-1979 (Box 48, Folder 344-346)
    - Organization and Planning: Supplementary Material, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 347)
    - Raintree, John B., 1978-1982 (Box 49, Folder 348-350)
    - Raintree, John B.: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 49, Folder 351)
    - Supplies and Equipment, 1965-1966, 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 352)
  - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), 116
    - Organization and Planning, 1970-1979 (Box 49, Folder 353, Box 50, Folder 354-358, Box 51, Folder 359)
    - Organization and Planning: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 51, Folder 360-361)
  - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology (ICIPE), 117
    - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology (ICIPE), 1969-1983 (Box 51, Folder 362-364, Box 52, Folder 365-370, Box 53, Folder 371-372)
    - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology (ICIPE) (Evaluation), 1975-1977, 1979-1981 (Box 53, Folder 373)
    - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology (ICIPE): Supplementary Material, undated (Box 53, Folder 374-376, Box 54, Folder 377)
  - International Agricultural Development Service (IADS), 119
    - Donation of Equipment, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 378)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - African Dilemmas - Conference, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 379)
      Title of conference: Ethnic Self-Determination and State Coherence: African Dilemmas
    - Aging and Retirement - Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 54, Folder 380)
      Conference title: Retirement and Aging: Cross-Cultural Perspectives
    - Antiparasitic Drugs - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 381)
      Conference title: Workshop in Antiparasitic Drug Design
    - Artists' Education and Career Entry - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 382)
      Conference title: The Professional Education and Career Entry of Artists in Europe and North America
    - CHILD-to-Child Programme - Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 54, Folder 383)
    - China Perspectives - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 54, Folder 384)
      Conference title: China in Asian and Global Perspectives
    - Chinese Law - Conference, 1979-1981 (Box 54, Folder 385)
      Conference title: The Transformation of Chinese Law, T'ang through Ming
    - Comite International de Liaison du Corps pour l'Alimentation (CILCA) - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 386)
      Conference title: From Principles to Practice: Village-Level Rural Development
    - Comite International de Liaison du Corps pour l'Alimentation (CILCA) - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 55, Folder 387-390)
    - Contemporary Mediterranean World - Conference, 1979-1983 (Box 55, Folder 391)
      Conference title: Stability and Change in the Mediterranean World: Prospects and Potentials
    - Diarrheal Diseases and Malnutrition - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 392)
      Conference title: Diarrhea and Malnutrition: Pathophysiology, Epidemiology and Interventions
    - East-West Policy Panel - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 393)
    - Educational Exchanges with China - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 55, Folder 394)
      Conference title: Academic Exchanges with the People's Republic of China
    - Energy Crisis of the 80's - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 395)
      Conference never held; proposed conference title: The Energy Crisis of the 80's and the Environmental Movement
    - Folk Law - Conference, 1979-1985, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 396)
      Conference title: State Institutions and Their Use of Folk Law: Theoretical and Practical Issues
    - Folk Law - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 56, Folder 397-398)
    - Genetics of Mosquito Disease Vectors - Conference, 1979-1983 (Box 56, Folder 399)
      Conference title: Recent Developments in the Genetics of Insect Vectors of Disease
    - Health Research in the Middle East - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 400)
      Conference title: Regional Scientific Cooperation for Health in Developing Countries
    - Higher Education and Foreign Student - Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 401)
      Conference title: Higher Education Reform: Implications for Foreign Students
    - Insect Science in Africa - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 402)
    - International Agricultural Research Systems - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 57, Folder 403)
      Conference title: Strengthening National Agricultural Research: The Role of International Associations
    - Islam and the West - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box 57, Folder 404)
      Conference title: Islam and the West: Revolution and Response
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Social Change - Conference, 1979-1983 (Box 57, Folder 405)
      Conference title: The Newer History and Perspectives on Social Change in Contemporary Society
      Folder 405 includes Evaluation
    - National Academy of Sciences - Chemical Safety - Conference, 1978-1981, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 406, Box 58, Folder 407)
      Conference title: International Group on the Safety Evaluation of Chemicals
    - National Academy of Sciences - Chemical Safety - Conference (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 58, Folder 408)
    - Neo-Confucianism in Korea - Conference, 1980-1981, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 409)
    - Neurology and Immunology - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 58, Folder 410)
      Conference title: Neurology and Immunology: Present Position and Future Prospects
    - New Energies in Developing Countries - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 411)
      Conference title: Use of New Energies in Developing Countries
    - Preparing Minority Youth for the Future - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box 58, Folder 412-413)
      Conference title: Preparing Youth of Emerging Technological Societies for the 21st Century: Health and Development Issues
    - Preparing Minority Youth for the Future - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 58, Folder 414, Box 59, Folder 415-417)
    - Primary Health Care - Conference, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 418-419)
      Conference title: Primary Health Care: Triaxial Recording of Physical, Psychological and Social Components
    - Primary Health Care - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 59, Folder 420, Box 60, Folder 421)
    - Resource Allocation and Health Technology - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box 60, Folder 422)
      Folder 422 contains Evaluation
      Conference title: Resource Allocation and Health Technology Assessment
    - Resource Allocation and Health Technology - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 60, Folder 423-424)
    - Rural Social Scientists in Africa - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 425)
      Conference title: Strategies to Meet Demands for Rural Social Scientists in Africa
    - Scholars - Allen, Samuel W., 1979-1981, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 426)
    - Scholars - Becquart-Leclercq, Jeannette, 1978-1984, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 427)
    - Scholars - Bénichou, Paul, 1980-1981, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 428)
    - Scholars - Blum, John M., 1979-1981, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 429)
    - Scholars - Bowers, John Z, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 430)
    - Scholars - Bowles, Samuel, 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 431)
    - Scholars - Breen, Timothy H., 1980-1981, 1983-1985, 1990, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 432)
    - Scholars - Brumbaugh, Robert S., 1980-1982 (Box 61, Folder 433)
    - Scholars - Bullard, Melissa Meriam, 1980-1982 (Box 61, Folder 434)
    - Scholars - Burke, Joseph C., 1980-1982 (Box 61, Folder 435)
    - Scholars - Candlish, M. Stewart, 1980-1982, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 436)
    - Scholars - Cisse, Aly, 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 437)
    - Scholars - Cope, Jackson I., 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 438)
    - Scholars - Cox, Kenneth R., 1980-1981, 1984, 1997, 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 439)
    - Scholars - Curry, Leslie, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 440)
    - Scholars - Curtis, Michael, 1979-1981, 1990, 1994-1995, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 441-442)
    - Scholars - Davenport, Horace W., 1979-1981 (Box 62, Folder 443)
    - Scholars - Davie, Donald, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 444)
    - Scholars - DeBenedetti, Charles, 1980-1981 (Box 62, Folder 445)
    - Scholars - De Gennaro, Richard, 1979-1982 (Box 62, Folder 446)
    - Scholars - Dell, Stephen, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 447)
    - Scholars - Dittrich, Paul-Heinz, 1980-1981, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 448)
    - Scholars - Duncan, J. Ann, 1980-1982, 1984, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 449)
    - Scholars - Elaigwa, J. Isawa, 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 450)
    - Scholars - Erlich, Victor, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 451)
    - Scholars - Fanger, Donald, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 452)
    - Scholars - Fowlie, Wallace, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 453)
    - Scholars - Fraenkel-Conrat, Heinz, 1979-1981, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 454)
    - Scholars - Frankenhaeuser, Marianne, 1979-1981, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 455)
    - Scholars - Gelber, Harry G., 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 456)
    - Scholars - Ghose, Sisirkumar, 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 457)
    - Scholars - Goffman, William, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 458)
    - Scholars - Goodman, Robert N., 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 459)
      Joint residency with Zoltan Kiraly and K. Roger Wood
    - Scholars - Grob, Gerald N., 1980-1981, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 460)
    - Scholars - Grunberger, Dezider, 1980-1981, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 461)
    - Scholars - Hall, Bruce F. and Lana L., 1980-1982 (Box 63, Folder 462)
      Joint residency
    - Scholars - Halperin, Samuel, 1979-1981, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 463)
    - Scholars - Harper, Margaret Carlyle (Peggy), 1979-1981, 1994, 1996-1997 (Box 64, Folder 464)
    - Scholars - Holland, James G., Jr., 1980-1982 (Box 64, Folder 465)
    - Scholars - Hunter, John R., 1979-1981 1983 (Box 64, Folder 466)
      Joint residency with John H. S. Blaxter
    - Scholars - Ichimura, Shinichi, 1980-1981, 1983-1984, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 467)
    - Scholars - Ichimura, Shinichi: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 64, Folder 468)
    - Scholars - Ilan, Eli, 1981-1982 (Box 64, Folder 469)
    - Scholars - Jacobson, Harold K., 1979-1984 (Box 64, Folder 470)
      Joint residency with Robert W. Cox
    - Scholars - Katz, Jay, 1980-1982, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 471)
    - Scholars - Kohansky, Mendel, 1980-1982 (Box 64, Folder 472)
    - Scholars - Kolb, Barbara, 1981-1983, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 473)
    - Scholars - Lewis, Robert Hall, 1980-1982 (Box 64, Folder 474)
    - Scholars - Lowenthal, Abraham F., 1980-1981, 1983, 1986, 2002-2003 (Box 65, Folder 475)
    - Scholars - Lubis, Mochtar, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 476)
    - Scholars - MacKenzie, Norman and Jeanne, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 477)
    - Scholars - McNaught, Kenneth W. K., 1980-1982 (Box 65, Folder 478)
    - Scholars - McVey, Ruth T., 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 479)
    - Scholars - Meier, Gerald M., 1981-1982, 1984, 2000-2001 (Box 65, Folder 480)
    - Scholars - Meller, Norman, 1979-1981, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 481)
    - Scholars - Meron, Theodor, 1980-1983 (Box 65, Folder 482)
    - Scholars - Middleton, Anne, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 483)
    - Scholars - Miller, Arthur S., 1980-1981, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 484)
    - Scholars - Miller, J. Hillis, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 485)
    - Scholars - Modelski, George, 1979-1981, 1983-1984 (Box 66, Folder 486)
    - Scholars - Nagy, András, 1979-1981, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 487)
    - Scholars - Nichols, Nina da Vinci, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 488)
    - Scholars - Paarlberg, Robert L., 1980-1982 (Box 66, Folder 489)
    - Scholars - Paarlberg, Robert L.: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 66, Folder 490)
    - Scholars - Perkins, James A., 1980-1982, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 491)
    - Scholars - Pines, James M., 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 492)
    - Scholars - Reed, John Shelton, 1980-1983, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 493)
    - Scholars - Rochlin, Gene I., 1980-1982 (Box 66, Folder 494)
    - Scholars - Rummel, Reinhardt, 1980-1981, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 495)
    - Scholars - Sahni, Krishna Kumar, 1979-1981, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 496)
    - Scholars - Seers, Dudley, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 497)
    - Scholars - Sen, Jyoti Prakash (J. P.), 1979-1983 (Box 67, Folder 498)
    - Scholars - Shankar, Patil S., 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 499)
    - Scholars - Solow, Robert M., 1979-1981 (Box 67, Folder 500)
    - Scholars - Stolley, Paul D., 1980-1982 (Box 67, Folder 501)
    - Scholars - Tagliabue, John, 1980-1984, 1986, 1989, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 502)
    - Scholars - Tajfel, Henri, 1979-1982 (Box 67, Folder 503)
    - Scholars - Targan, Barry, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 504)
    - Scholars - Terr, Lenore C., 1979-1982 (Box 67, Folder 505)
    - Scholars - Treverton, Gregory F., 1978, 1981-1982 (Box 67, Folder 506)
    - Scholars - Ussachevsky, Vladimir A., 1981-1982 (Box 67, Folder 507)
    - Scholars - Vorenberg, James, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 508)
    - Scholars - Walsh, Julia A., 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 509)
    - Scholars - Wanshel, Jeff, 1979-1981, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 510)
    - Scholars - Warnke, Frank J., 1979-1982, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 511)
    - Scholars - Watson, Ronald R., 1979-1981 (Box 68, Folder 512)
    - Scholars - Weitz, Margaret Collins, 1980-1981, 1985, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 513)
    - Scholars - Weitzman, Lenore J., 1978-1982, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 514)
    - Scholars - Zubrzycki, Jerzy, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 515)
    - Scientific Concepts of Time - Conference, 1979-1983, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 516)
      Conference title: Scientific Concepts of Time in Humanistic and Social Perspectives
    - Technical Aids for the Disabled - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box 68, Folder 517)
      Conference title: International Conference on Information Systems for Technical Aids for People with Disabilities
    - Trade Restrictions - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 518)
      Conference title: Restrictions on Transactions in the International Market for Services
    - U.S.-Soviet Relations in the 1980's - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 519)
    - University and International Value Consensus - Conference, 1978-1982, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 520-521)
      Conference title: The Role of the University in Seeking International Value Consensus
    - University and International Value Consensus - Conference: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 69, Folder 522)
    - World Literature - Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 69, Folder 523)
      Conference title: The Collective Implementation of a Pilot Curriculum in World Literature
  - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, 150
    - Evaluators, 1973-1977 (Box 69, Folder 524)
    - Evaluators (B-D), 1974-1976 (Box 70, Folder 525)
    - Evaluators (E-G), 1973-1975 (Box 70, Folder 526)
    - Evaluators - Goldstein, Sidney, 1974-1977 (Box 70, Folder 527)
    - Evaluators (H-I), 1973-1975 (Box 70, Folder 528)
    - Evaluators - Hodge, Robert, 1973-1979 (Box 70, Folder 529)
    - Evaluators (M-P), 1973-1977 (Box 70, Folder 530)
    - Evaluators (R-W), 1973-1977 (Box 70, Folder 531)
    - Inquiries, 1974-1975 (Box 71, Folder 532)
    - Inquiries (A-D), 1972-1975 (Box 71, Folder 533)
    - Inquiries (E-J), 1973-1975 (Box 71, Folder 534)
    - Inquiries (K-O), 1972-1976 (Box 71, Folder 535)
    - Inquiries (P-Z), 1973-1975 (Box 71, Folder 536)
    - Referrals (A-Z), 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 537)
    - Florida, 211
      - Sly, David F., 1978-1982 (Box 71, Folder 538-539)
        Research title: The Formation of Migration Expectations
    - Massachusetts, 224
      - Aquino, Felix J., 1978-1981, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 540-541)
        Research title: Information and Migration: A Spanish Case
      - Aquino, Felix J.: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 72, Folder 542)
      - Rogers, Rosemarie, 1975-1983 (Box 72, Folder 543-544)
        Project title: Return Migration to Yugoslavia: Policies, the Innovative Return Migrant, and Prospects for Economic Development
      - Rogers, Rosemarie (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 72, Folder 545)
      - Rogers, Rosemarie: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 72, Folder 546, Box 73, Folder 547)
    - New York, 235
      - Min, Kyonghee, 1978-1982 (Box 73, Folder 548)
        Research title: Urban Growth, Migration and Labor Force Utilization in Korea, 1960-1970
      - Min, Kyonghee: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 73, Folder 549-550)
    - North Carolina, 236
      - Aghajanian, Akbar, 1977-1982 (Box 73, Folder 551)
        Research title: Fertility and Economic Value of Children: A Pilot Study in Rural Communities of Iran
      - Aghajanian, Akbar (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 73, Folder 552)
      - Turchi, Boone A., 1978-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 553)
        Research title: Population Policy, Food and the Financial Cost of Children in Colombia
    - Ohio, 238
      - Kelley, Samuel C., 1979-1982 (Box 74, Folder 554)
        Research title: Internal Migration and Decentralization Policy in Venezuela
      - Tien, H. Yuan, 1978-1982 (Box 74, Folder 555)
        Research title: Accelerated Farm Mechanization and Rural Population Change in the People's Republic of China
    - Peru, 331
      - Asociación Multidisciplinaria de Investigación y Docencia en Población (AMIDEP) - Fertility Workshop, 1979-1982 (Box 74, Folder 556-557)
      - Asociación Multidisciplinaria de Investigación y Docencia en Población (AMIDEP) - Fertility Workshop: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 74, Folder 558, Box 75, Folder 559)
    - England, 401
      - Mauskopf, Josephine, 1979-1981 (Box 75, Folder 560-561)
        Research title: A Study of Brazilian Fertility with Special Attention to the Spurious Correlation Problem in Measuring the Replacement of Lost Children Within Families
    - Nepal, 474
      - Uprety, Hari Nandan, 1978-1981, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 562)
        Research title: The Impact of Integrated Health and Family Planning Services on Fertility Behavior in Two Districts of Nepal
    - Gold Coast, 496
      - Oppong, Christine, 1976-1982 (Box 75, Folder 563)
        Research title: Women's Roles and Fertility in West Africa: A Biographical Approach
      - Oppong, Christine (Evaluation), 1977 (Box 75, Folder 564)
      - Oppong, Christine: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 76, Folder 565-566)
    - Korea, 613
      - Lee, Hyo-Chae, 1977-1982 (Box 76, Folder 567)
        Research title: Marriage and Women's Labor Force Participation in Korea
      - Lee, Hyo-Chae (Evaluation), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 568)
      - Lee, Hyo-Chae: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 76, Folder 569)
    - Indonesia, 652
      - Hugo, Graeme J., 1978-1979,1981 (Box 77, Folder 570)
        Research title: Population Mobility and Development in Indonesia
  - Demographic Evaluation Projects, 151
    - North Carolina, 236
      - University of North Carolina - Demographic Research Consortium, 1978-1984, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 571-573)
    - Brazil, 305
      - Population Statistics - Henriques, Maria Helena F. T., 1978-1983 (Box 77, Folder 574-575, Box 78, Folder 576)
      - Population Statistics - Henriques, Maria Helena F. T.: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 78, Folder 577)
    - Nigeria, 497
      - University of Calabar - Uyanga, Joseph, 1977-1982 (Box 78, Folder 578-580)
  - Unemployment and Human Resource Utilization, 152
    - Argentina, 301
      - Instituto Torcuato Di Tella - Latin American Employment, 1971-1979 (Box 78, Folder 581, Box 79, Folder 582)
      - Instituto Torcuato Di Tella - Latin American Employment (Evaluation), 1975, 1981, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 583)
      - Instituto Torcuato Di Tella - Latin American Employment: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 79, Folder 584-587, Box 80, Folder 588-589)
  - Comité Permanent Inter-Etats de Lutte Contre la Sécheresse dans le Sahel (CILSS), 165
    Permanent Interstate Committee for Drought Control in the Sahel
    - Permanent Interstate Committee for Drought Control in the Sahel, 1980-1982 (Box 80, Folder 590-591)
      Comité Permanent Inter-Etats de Lutte Contre la Sécheresse dans le Sahel (CILSS)
    - Permanent Interstate Committee for Drought Control in the Sahel: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 80, Folder 592-593, Box 81, Folder 594-595)
  - Research Fellowship for Minority-Group Scholars, 175
    - Fellowships, Scholarships,Training Awards, E
      - Bacon, Mary M., 1979-1983 (Box 81, Folder 596)
        Research title: Identifying the Gifted and Talented: Culturally Relevant Assessment and Programming Strategies for Low SES Black Youth
      - Bruce-Novoa, John D., 1979-1981 (Box 81, Folder 597)
        Research title: The Chicano Novel, A Study of Its Thematic and Structural Paradigm
        Folder 597 contains Evaluation
      - Casas, J. Manuel, 1980-1981 (Box 81, Folder 598, Box 82, Folder 599)
        Research title: Social Interactional Strengths of Mexican-American Families
      - Castillo, Pedro, 1980-1983 (Box 82, Folder 600)
        Research title: Chicanos and the City: A Comparative Analysis of the Development of the Barrio in Los Angeles, San Antonio and Chicago
      - Christian, Charles M., 1980-1982 (Box 82, Folder 601)
        Research title: The Employment Problems of Blacks, Hispanics and Women in State and Local Government
      - Christian, Charles M.: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 82, Folder 602-603)
      - Combs, Michael W., 1980-1982 (Box 82, Folder 604)
        Research title: The Courts of Appeals in the Political Process: The Case of Racial Segregation in Northern Public Schools
      - Garcia, Philip, 1979-1982 (Box 82, Folder 605)
        Research title: Length of Residence and English-Speaking Acquisition as Determinants of Socioeconomic Attainments Among Mexican-Origin Adults
      - Gates, Henry Louis, Jr., 1980-1983 (Box 82, Folder 606)
        Research title: The Idea of Blackness in Western Cricital Theory: The Enlightenment
      - Gavillán-Torres, Eva M., 1979-1982, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 607)
        Research title: A Critical Review of Language Assessment Practices for the Placement of Hispanic Children in the Least Restrictive Environments
      - Harris, Robert L., Jr., 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 608)
        Research title: Afro-Americans and the United Nations: Petitions for Freedom and Justice
        Folder 608 contains Evaluation
      - Lozano, Anthony G., 1979-1981 (Box 83, Folder 609)
        Folder 609 contains Evaluation
        Research title: The Spanish Language in the United States: A Cultural and Linguistic History
      - Matute-Bianchi, Marie Eugenia, 1979-1983, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 610)
        Research title: School Desegregation, Bilingual Education and Mexican American Children in California
      - Morse, Roberta Naomi, 1980-1981 (Box 83, Folder 611)
        Research title: The Impact of Study Skills Training and Therapy Approaches on Black Test-Anxious College Students